I mean, I guess folks have become so unable to tell what's real or not, whether it's AI
or people that you can't even tell when someone's asking a genuine question.
This is why I be taking breaks from social media because y'all are annoying as hell.
It's like I show up here every day, honest and true and real.
And then I'm still met with, are you asking for real?
Or this is a disingenuous question.
I asked, what are the protests about in it on?
This is what it looks like to me.
Let me know.
And I get all sorts of nonsense.
This is what the problem is.
People are showing genuine interest and then you get all sorts of nonsense.
Just answer the goddamn question.
And now you're not going to hear from me for the rest of the day because y'all are so fucking annoying.
So talk amongst yourselves.